#source residences.odl
#date Tue Jul 13 09:58:27 GMT 1999
#copyright Ogalala Ltd
#import THING ROOM
#export ATRIUM PORCH


# # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # #

# $Id: residences.odl,v 1.1 1999/03/09 15:40:24 alex Exp $
# Definitions associated with the Residential system
# Alexander Veenendaal, 4th Feburary 1999
# Copyright (C) HotGen Studios Ltd <www.hotgen.com>


#------------------------------- Atrium --------------------------------#
## Rooms that inherit from atrium are given the ability to address the numerous
## apartments that belong to it. As there may be many (~40) residences, normal
## methods of travel cannot possibly work here. Instead, the commands will take
## the form of "go to room 40" "enter apartment 12" etc.
##
## The associated command with this atom is the !GenerateAtrium command, which in
## a nutshell, takes an existing room and 'atriumises' it, adding the numerous
## porches (leading to the residences).
!atom atrium thing

## overrides the basic go, to interpret the room numbers within the command
#container_go		= !AtriumGo

!set atrium.numeric_go !AtriumGo

!set atrium.on_exit !AtriumGo

## the number of residences attached to this atrium
!set atrium.residence_count 0

## a table of porch room ids along with their respective apartment numbers
## for example [ 1=room23 2=room24 3=room25 4=room26 ]
## this is used by the atriums special go function.
!set atrium.porch_table null

##Error message for the creation of residences.
!set atrium.no_porch_msg "There appears to be no apartment of that number."

##A message used by the create residence command which is suggested when an invalid
##exit argument is supplied
!set atrium.invalid_exit_msg "The proposed exit type does not exist."

# # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # #




## Porches are autogenerated as part of the atrium creation.
!atom porch room

## The atrium room that this porch is off
!set porch.atrium null

## The exit table which points to the atrium
!set porch.atriumExit null

## The residence *place* that this particular porch leads to
!set porch.residence null

## The exit table which points to the home
!set porch.residenceExit null

## The kind of exit type for the entrance to the residence
#residenceExitType	= $exit

## The description will automatically include the apartment number
!set porch.description_root "You are standing outside number"

